YouTube has taken away the option to do
live videos until you have a thousand
subscribers so I'm gonna record until
you get the thousand subscribers but
record live and publish because that's
what I'm capable of today's this week's
blog post is called the power trifecta
we already have it it's quite a littler
we already hold all of the power needed
to change our society for the better we
the people hold the power collectively
in three major areas of life we are the
voters we are the consumer / user we are
the Labour when we stop allowing the
powers that be to divide us and instead
find out what we have in common and work
from there we the people are unstoppable
for each of these three areas I will
explain briefly why they are currently
broken what we have in common at our
core what a society we can run together
for our collective benefit could look
like and some technology projects that
can help us gather and use our
collective power for our collective good
voters our democracies are currently
working in the corporations and
politicians best interest and not the
people they represents best interest the
media is owned by the rich and powerful
and they are incentivized to keep the
system as is what we have in common no
matter where on the political spectrum
we are is that we all want politicians
we can trust who look out for their
constituents best interests we want true
representation a political party that
directly represents the people votes how
they would vote on every issue could
sweep the elections if we believed they
could the media tells us it's not
possible
so we both status quo instead a world
where our politicians have to be honest
and act with transparency where they are
held accountable to the will of the
people they represent is possible when
we have access to information that is
trustworthy and usable projects IMDB for
politicians track the money from donors
see if the platforms they were elected
on were upheld their past job experience
and performance etc ie information on
politicians like we have on actors
we can a different project can be to
track the stats accurately between
administrations to best be able to
compare them ie the unemployment rate
time spent on golf trips GDP taxes etc
or a fantasy political game using our
actual world world politicians that
engages people in politics for the
benefit of the masses making it fun and
easy to stay informed we are running a
corporation with complete democracy and
transparency this in and of itself is a
revolutionary act as we showcase it is
possible and yields amazing results we
are not gonna sit back and allow our
democracies to exist in their current
corrupt and secret state we will demand
better because we can see better as
possible the consumer / user because I
hate the word consumer nearly every
dollar at the top comes from the bottom
we vote with our wallets every time we
buy something the information we have to
work on is often only the branding and
marketing from the company itself much
of the information is already available
it just is not organized to make it
usable ie ingredients on every package
we want inexpensive fast and good
quality goods and when we create these
together less money is going to profit
shareholders and more is redistributed
into these values we will still have
diverse products because we have
different wants and needs but by making
them together we can create better
products that do not cost the planet or
create human misery together we can
assess every product on the market for
the values we want to uphold by
inputting the ingredients the longevity
of the product costs our use etc we can
track the companies and their products
and see the truth over the spin projects
a food and beauty product products
ingredients like the good guide which
exists but transparent and crowd-sourced
so anyone can input any new product or
company and the user can easily compare
products to see which ones align with
their values we can also see holes in
the market that we can create solutions
for together ie if there wasn't a vegan
kosher body wash we do not cease the
means of production we don't cease don't
take it over we recreate it as it makes
sense to do so when the financial
thresholds are met the workers we do the
vast majority of the physical emotional
and mental labor that our society
thrives on yet our wages have not kept
up with inflation that money has been
siphoned off and given to shareholders
as automation and outsourcing cost
people jobs our globe faces massive
unemployment we all want to be able to
contribute to society and we want our
families to be provided for currently
these are tied together in a Jo B as we
create solutions together to make sure
our members are fed clothed and housed
they are given freedom freedom from the
need to work or starve as people no
longer have to work the supply of labour
diminishes internally our company we
rely heavily on volunteer crowdsource
labor by tapping into people to flow and
offering them the tools to contribute in
a way that is its own reward I wrote an
entire blog post about this called
it can be easy which I will link in the
description as we get more free labor as
we get more free labor
we are also costing the for-profit
companies more money as we reduce their
labor force people will not work for $10
an hour when they have their needs met
to leave the work you are choosing to do
for free because it is your flow and
your genius you have to get paid a lot
imagine you are living your best life
with people who get you contributing to
groups you were part of in a way that
works for you and the group how much are
you going to need to get paid to go
focus on some for-profit companies
vision over your own projects a food
platform that helps people combine
purchasing power and labor to create
more efficiency for willing participants
people trade time or money to get access
to food systems that they want to
participate in I'll do an entire blog
post on that at one point our
marketplace platform enables people to
create their own jobs out of their
houses for fair compensation example
instead of there being dozens of
cleaning services per city where
customers pay $25 an hour and workers
make $15 an hour with the added profit
going to management
and to maintain the company we can
create have one company platform that
facilitates the transactions between
cleaners and people hiring them so that
the vast majority of the money goes
directly to the cleaner the platform
takes care of all the other work ie
marketing scheduling insurance etc all
of the ad hoc piecemeal work laborers
are doing to make ends meet
uber doordash TaskRabbit etc can be
recreated with the worker and user in
mind with more money going into the
labor and no money going to a for-profit
company and its shareholders there would
be a small transaction fee agreed on by
all that is taken to maintain the system
when we have the tools to utilize our
collective power it becomes inevitable
that we create a world of peace and
abundance for everyone we already have
the power as voters users and workers
we just need to organize and then it can
be done easily with tech and that can be
done easily with technology when we
realize the base of the pyramid has the
power we turn it on its head and the
power dynamics topple please like and
subscribe hit the bell we are gonna
change the world together and I'm gonna
get 2,000 subscribers so that we can go
live and start the technology company
that is going to make all of our lives
better
take care